[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "AはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "able",
    "explanation": "Aは'ABLE'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "BはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "baker",
    "explanation": "Bは'BAKER'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "CはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "charlie",
    "explanation": "Cは'CHARLIE'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "DはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "delta",
    "explanation": "Dは'DELTA'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "EはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "echo",
    "explanation": "Eは'ECHO'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "FはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "fox",
    "explanation": "Fは'FOX'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "GはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "george",
    "explanation": "Gは'GEORGE'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "HはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "how",
    "explanation": "Hは'HOW'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "IはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "item",
    "explanation": "Iは'ITEM'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "JはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "jack",
    "explanation": "Jは'JACK'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "KはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "king",
    "explanation": "Kは'KING'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "LはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "love",
    "explanation": "Lは'LOVE'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "MはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "mike",
    "explanation": "Mは'MIKE'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "NはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "nancy",
    "explanation": "Nは'NANCY'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "OはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "over",
    "explanation": "Oは'OVER'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "PはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "peter",
    "explanation": "Pは'PETER'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "QはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "queen",
    "explanation": "Qは'QUEEN'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "RはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "roger",
    "explanation": "Rは'ROGER'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "SはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "sugar",
    "explanation": "Sは'SUGAR'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "TはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "tiger",
    "explanation": "Tは'Tiger'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "UはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "uncle",
    "explanation": "Uは'UNCLE'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "VはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "victory",
    "explanation": "Vは'VICTORY'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "WはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "whisky",
    "explanation": "Wは'WHISKY'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "XはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "x-ray",
    "explanation": "Xは'X-RAY'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "YはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "york",
    "explanation": "Yは'YORK'です。"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "ZはIATAフォネティックコードで何？(全て小文字で答えよ)",
    "answer": "zebra",
    "explanation": "Zは'ZEBRA'です。"
  }
]
